MOBILE DEVELOPER · WEB DEVELOPE

□ (+254) 700099026 | ■ leviopunga@gmail.com | # levi-levi-opunga.vercel.app/ | □ Levi-Opunga | □ levi-baraka

"The best way to predict the future is to invent it"

Summary

I'm a Computer Science grad student specializing in the back-end development and Android. As you can guess I'm a super nerd who loves Vim, Linux and OS X and enjoys to customize all of the development environment. Interested in devising a better problem-solving method for challenging tasks, and learning new technologies and tools if the need arises.

Skills

Back-end SpringBoot, Spark,TRPC, REST API

Mobile Java and Kotlin Android , React Native (learning)
 Front-end Programming
 JAVA,Kotlin ,SQL ,Ocaml, Typescript, ShellScript, C/C++

Collaboration Git, Agile and Scrum methods, Notion

Other Competencies LaTeX,Docker, Linux,VmWare,Vitrualbox,FireBase

Spoken Languages English, Swahili

Education

MMU(Multimedia University of Kenya)

Nairobi, Kenya

B.S. IN COMPUTER SCIENCE

Sept. 2021 - Present

· Ongiong

Moringa School Nairobi, Kenya

Moringa school certificate in Software Development For Android and Angular

2021-2022

- Started in 2021 took a break to join campus and finished during long holiday in August 2022
- · Cerificate Link

UHS(Upperhill School)

Nairobi, Kenya

HIGH SCHOOL DIPLOMA(KCSE)

2017 - 2021

- Delay of one year due to effects of the Covid-19 pandemic
- · Attained an overall grade of A-

Projects

CLOSET APP

Java Android, Firebase, Retrofit

.

2022

- · An application to get inspiration for outfits and save the ones you like on firebase
- · To be intergated with revery ai which an api that allows for generation of outfits using input images for better user experience
- Github Repository

The Watchlist Java Android, Firebase, Retrofit

Арр

2022

An application using the New York Times api to provide movie reviews and summary. Allows users to leave comments on review and save
movies to their list

Github Repositoryy

Contacts Management Site

SpringBoot,Postgresql,React

,NextJS

Website 2022

A site to demonstrate basic CRUD and Database AUTH functionally using a springboot backend and nextis frontend. It utilises spring data jdbc
and hikari pooling for database connectivity

• Frontend : Github Repository

· Backend: Github Repository

News Api Java Spark ,Postgresql

API

Github Repository

E-commerce Product page Next Js, Tailwind Css

WEBSITE

• A frontend site built with NextJs 13 with both sever side componets and client side components

· An api implementing crud operations for a company with staff, news, and departments as database objects

- Github Repository
- · Click To View On Vercel

 Tip Calculator
 Alpine Js ,HTML5 ,Taiwind

ALPINE JS APP

- · An Alpine Js appliction for calculating tips among individuals styled using tailwind css
- Github Repository
- Click To View On Github Pages

Text Editor Java, Swing

Java Desktop Application

- · A fully funtional text editor written from scratch with java swing and flatlaf for styling
- The repo also includes a python supervised learning project for gender detection using opency and numpy
- Click To View Github Repository
- Click To Download Release From Github

Quotes AppAngular Typescript

ANGULAR APP 2021

- An angular application that allows user to add, delete, upvote, downvote quotes
- · Open Github Repo
- · Site: Click To View on Netlify

Work Experience

Upwork, Fivver Online

FREELANCE DEVELOPER 2021 - Present

• Gained work experience working as a freelance software developer on remote jobs

Extracurricular Activity

CIT Club(Computing and Information Technology Club)

Kenya SEPT. 2021 - PRESENT

2022

2022

• Gained expertise in mentorship from alumni and from bootcamps organised by the club.

• Currently participating as a Java technical lead teaching SpringBoot and android Concepts to members

Angular Kenya Kenya Kenya

MEMBER Jun. 2022 - PRESENT

- · Gained experience listening to industry experts give talks on various fields especially on front-end development
- Won angular Kenya merchandise in a debugging contest

Referees

Donata Akinyi Nairobi, Kenya

FRONT-END ENGINEER Carepay International

• Email: Akinyidonattah@gmail.com

Future Interests_

Languages Haskell, Clojure, Python, Go, Rust

Feilds Deep learning and Neural networks, KMM, Rust System development, Functional Programming